Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 197990; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Production: Corporate: 1949-1950, 198250 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 1)
  - Production: Corporate: 1951-1960, 198249 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs: 1937-1941: Corporate: Publicity, 198248 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs: 1942: Corporate: Publicity (Including white feather campaign), 198247 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs: 1942-1945: Corporate: War Task Department, 198246 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs: 1942: Corporate: "Report on the Public Relations of Time Inc" by Ivy Lee & T.J. Ross, 198245 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs: 1943 & Before: Corporate: Miscellaneous, 198244 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 8-9)
  - Public Affairs: 1960 & Before: Corporate: Miscellaneous, 198243 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 12-13)
  - Public Affairs: 1943-1950: Corporate: Publicity, 198242 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs: 1951-1959: Corporate: Publicity, 198241 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 11)
  - Public Affairs: 1960: Corporate: Publicity, 198240 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 14)
  - Radio [empty], 198239 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 15)
  - Saturday Review of Literature [empty], 198238 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 16)
  - Silver Burdett [empty], 198237 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: July and before, 198236 (Offsite-box 863, Folder 1-2)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: August-October, 198235 (Offsite-box 443)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: August-October [RESTRICTED], 198234 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953: Pre-Publication: November-December, 198233 (Offsite-box 863, Folder 3)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: January-February, 198232 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 19)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: March-May, 198231 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Pre-Publication: June-July, 198230 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: August-December, 198229 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Boxing Scandal, 198228 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Comment (Response to 1st Issue), 198227 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Edit: Comment (Response to 1st Issue to HRL), 198226 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: August-December, 198225 (Offsite-box 443, Folder 26)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: Circulation Promotion, 198224 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 1)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1954: Publishing: Promotion, 198223 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 2)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: January-May, 198222 (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: January-May [RESTRICTED], 198221 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: June-December, 198220 (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: June-December [RESTRICTED], 198219 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Edit: Comment: First Anniversary, 198218 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 5)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Prospectus (HRL Letter to Leo Burnett), 198217 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 6)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Publishing: January-May, 198216 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 7)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1955: Publishing: June-December, 198215 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 8)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Edit: January-May, 198214 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 9)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Edit: June-December, 198213 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 10)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: January-May, 198212 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 11)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: June-December, 198211 (Offsite-box 444)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1956: Publishing: June-December [RESTRICTED], 198210 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1957: Edit, 198209 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 13)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1957: Publishing, 198208 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 14)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Edit: January-June, 198207 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 15)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Edit: July-December, 198206 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 16)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1958: Publishing, 198205 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 17)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: January-August, 198204 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 18)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: September-December, 198203 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 19-20)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1959: Edit: Publishing, 198202 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 21)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1953-1960: Hank Brennan's critiques, 198201 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 22)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: July-December, 198200 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 23)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: January-June, 198199 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 24)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Edit: Laguerre Mockup, 198198 (Offsite-box 444, Folder 25)
  - Sports Illustrated: 1960: Publishing, 198197 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 1)
  - Syndication: 1930-1935, 198196 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 2)
  - Syndication: 1956-1960, 198195 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 3)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1941-1951, 198194 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 4)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1952-1955, 198193 (Offsite-box 445)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1952-1955 [RESTRICTED], 198192 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Temple-Eastex, Inc.: 1956-1960, 198191 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 6)
  - Tide, 198190 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 7)
  - Time: Forerunners, 198189 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1922 &Before: Edit, 198188 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 9-10)
  - Time: 1922: Edit: Dummy (Specimen Issue) 12/30/1922, 198187 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1922: Edit: Prospectus, 198186 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1923: Circulation Promotion, 198185 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run, 1/6/23: Pages 1-60, 198184 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run, 1/6/23: Pages 61-114, 198183 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 15)
  - Time:1923: Edit: First Issue 3/3/23, 198182 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Comment, 198181 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1923: Edit: Dry Run 1/6/23: Copy, 198180 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1923: Publishing, 198179 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1924: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198178 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1924: Publishing, 198177 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1926: Edit, 198176 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1926: Publishing, 198175 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1926: Publishing, 198174 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1927: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198173 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1927: Edit: Style, 198172 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Production, 198171 (Offsite-box 445)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Production [RESTRICTED], 198170 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Jan.-Aug., 198169 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1927: Publishing: Sept.-Dec., 198168 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1928: Edit, 198167 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 30)
  - Time: 1928: Edit: Style, 198166 (Offsite-box 445, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Market Research: "Do You Own A Horse?", 198165 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Jan.-March, 198164 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: April-June, 198163 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: July-Sept., 198162 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1928: Publishing: Oct.-Dec., 198161 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1929: Edit, 198160 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1929: Publishing: Perpetual Subscription Offer, 198159 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1929: Publishing: Miscellaneous, 198158 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1930: Edit, 198157 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1930: Publishing, 198156 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1931: Edit, 198155 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1931: Publishing, 198154 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1932: Edit, 198153 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 13)
  - Time: Publishing: Appleton Survey, 198152 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 14-15)
  - Time: 1932: Publishing, 198151 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1933: Publishing, 198150 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1933: Edit, 198149 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1934-1936: Edit: Pictures, 198148 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 19-20)
  - Time: 1934: Edit, 198147 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1934: Edit: "Lindburgh Case", 198146 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1934: Publishing, 198145 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1935: Edit, 198144 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1935: Publishing, 198143 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1936: Edit, 198142 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1936: Publishing, 198141 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1937: Publishing, 198140 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1937: Edit: Style, 198139 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1937: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198138 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 30)
  - Time: Edit: Ingersoll Prospectus, 198137 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1938: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198136 (Offsite-box 446, Folder 32-33)
  - Time: 1938: Edit: Style, 198135 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 1-2)
  - Time: 1938: 15th Anniversary, 198134 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1938: Publishing, 198133 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 4-5)
  - Time: 1938 &Before: Edit: HRL Undated Memos, 198132 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Background for War, 198131 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 7-8)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Reaction to Promotion Book March of Time, 198130 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: HRL Marked Copy, 198129 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Time The War & Truth, 198128 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Jan.-April, 198127 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: May-April, 198126 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Oct.-Dec., 198125 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 14-15)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Comment, 198124 (Offsite-box 447)
  - Time: 1939: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED], 198123 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1939: Publishing, 198122 (Offsite-box 447)
  - Time: 1939: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 198121 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Jan.-June, 198120 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: July-Dec., 198119 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Comment, 198118 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Style, 198117 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1940: Publishing, 198116 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1940: Edit: Staff Meeting, 198115 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Style, 198114 (Offsite-box 447, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198113 (Offsite-box 447-448)
  - Time: 1941: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198112 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1941: Publishing, 198111 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Air Power Story, 9/42, 198110 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Comment, 198109 (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Comment [RESTRICTED], 198108 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Organization, 198107 (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Organization [RESTRICTED], 198106 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: World to Come Experiment, 198105 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 6)
  - Time: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198104 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1942: Publishing, 198103 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment (Reports), 198102 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198101 (Offsite-box 448)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198100 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Organization: Jan.-Aug., 198099 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Organization: Sept.-Dec., 198098 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 12-13)
  - Time: 1943: Publishing, 198097 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1943: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198096 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 15-16)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment, 198095 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment (Reports), 198094 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198093 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Controversy: Foreign News, 198092 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198091 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Organization, 198090 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 22-23)
  - Time: 1944: Edit: Style, 198089 (Offsite-box 448, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1944: Publishing: Mind Power Campaign, 198088 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1944: Publishing: Miscellaneous, 198087 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 2)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Comment (Reports), 198086 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 3)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198085 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Controversy: Foreign News, 198084 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Organization, 198083 (Offsite-box 449)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Organization [RESTRICTED], 198082 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198081 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 7)
  - Time: 1945-1949: Edit: HRL: undated, handwritten memos, 198080 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1945: Publishing, 198079 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Style, 198078 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198077 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Organization, 198076 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Boyce Prices Reports, 198075 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1946: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198074 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1946: Publishing, 198073 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198072 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 16)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Organization, 198071 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 17)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198070 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 18)
  - Time: 1947: Publishing, 198069 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 19)
  - Time: 1948: Anniversary, 25th, 198068 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 20)
  - Time: 1948: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198067 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1947: Edit: Boyce Price's Reports, 198066 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1948: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198065 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 23)
  - Time: 1948: Publishing, 198064 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 24)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198063 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198062 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Staff suggestions for improvement: A-M, 198061 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Staff suggestions for improvement: N-Z, 198060 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1949: Edit: Organization: Miscellaneous, 198059 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1949: Publishing, 198058 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 30)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198057 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 31)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Comment: (5/22) Ruth Page Ballet Co., 198056 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 32)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Comment: Miscellaneous, 198055 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 33)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: Organization, 198054 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 34)
  - Time: 1950: Edit: They Say Experiment, 198053 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 35)
  - Time: 1950: Publishing, 198052 (Offsite-box 449, Folder 36)
  - Time: 1951: Edit: Comment, 198051 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 1)
  - Time: 1951: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198050 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 2-3)
  - Time: 1951: Publishing, 198049 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Comment, 198048 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 5)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Mullen Investment Company (1/21), 198047 (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Mullen Investment Company (1/21) [RESTRICTED], 198046 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198045 (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1952: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198044 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1952: Publishing, 198043 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 8)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Comment, 198042 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 9)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198041 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 10)
  - Time: 1953: Edit: Opinion Experiment, 198040 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 11)
  - Time: 1953: Publishing, 198039 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 12)
  - Time: 1954: Edit: Comment, 198038 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1954: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198037 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 14)
  - Time: 1954: Publishing, 198036 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 15)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198035 (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 198034 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1955: Edit: Comment, 198033 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 17)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: America, 198032 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 18)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Organization, 198031 (Offsite-box 450)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Organization [RESTRICTED], 198030 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Time: 1955: Publishing, 198029 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 20)
  - Time: Edit: 1955: Miscellaneous, 198028 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 23-24)
  - Time: 1956: Edit: Comment, 198027 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 21)
  - Time: 1956: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198026 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 22)
  - Time: 1956: Publishing, 198025 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 25)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Quiz Show Scandal, 198024 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 26)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Comment, 198023 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 27)
  - Time: 1957: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198022 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 28)
  - Time: 1957: Publishing, 198021 (Offsite-box 450, Folder 29)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Comment, 198020 (Offsite-box 450-451)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198019 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 2-3)
  - Time: 1958: Edit: Publishing, 198018 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 4)
  - Time: 1959: Edit: Comment, 198017 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 5-6)
  - Time: 1959: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198016 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 7-8)
  - Time: 1959: Publishing, 198015 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 9-10)
  - Time: 1960: Edit: Comment, 198014 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 11-12)
  - Time: 1960: Edit: Miscellaneous, 198013 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 13)
  - Time: 1960: Publishing, 198012 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 14)
  - Time International: 1940 &Before, 198011 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 15)
  - Time International: 1941: Jan.-March, 198010 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 16)
  - Time International: 1941: April-Dec., 198009 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 17-18)
  - Time International: 1942, 198008 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 19)
  - Time International: 1943, 198007 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 20-21)
  - Time International: 1944-1945, 198006 (Offsite-box 451, Folder 22-23)
  - Time International: 1946-1960, 198005 (Offsite-box 451-452)
  - Time-Life Books: 1943-1957, 198004 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 2)
  - Time-Life Books: 1958, 198003 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 3)
  - Time-Life Books: 1959-1960, 198002 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 4)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: 1950 & Before, 198001 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 5-6)
  - Time-Life Broadcast: 1951-1960, 198000 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 7-8)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1923-1936, 197999 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1937-1941, 197998 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 10-11)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1942-1946, 197997 (Offsite-box 452)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1942-1946 [RESTRICTED], 197996 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1947-1950, 197995 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 14-15)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1944: Excess Profits Tax, 197994 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1951-1954, 197993 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1955-1956, 197992 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Office: 1957-1960, 197991 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 19)
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 196504; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - All You, 197989 (Offsite-box 452, Folder 20)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1961-1970, 197988 (Offsite-box 452-453)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1971-1989, 197987 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 2)
  - Advertising, Corporate, 197986 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 3-4)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Advertiser's Inserts, 197985 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 5)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Campaigns: Before 1964, 197984 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 6)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Campaigns: 1970-1985, 197983 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 7)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Corporate Discounts, 197982 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 8)
  - Advertising, Corporate: Federal Trade Commission Hearing: 1971, 197981 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 9)
  - Advertising, Corporate: NYC Advertising Tax: 1971, 197980 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 10)
  - America Online: 2002: Washington Post Series: 7/18-7/19, 197979 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 11)
  - American Health Corporation, 197978 (Offsite-box 453)
  - American Health Corporation [RESTRICTED], 197977 (Offsite-box R4)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1977-1982, 197976 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 14-15)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1983-1983, 197975 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 16-17)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 1987-7/1988, 197974 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 18)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): 8/1988-, 197973 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 19)
  - American Television & Communications (ATC): Preview Subscription Television, Inc., 197972 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 20)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1960-1962, 197971 (Offsite-box 453, Folder 21-22)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1963 &Later, 197970 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 1)
  - Asiaweek, 197969 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors: 1961-1978, 197968 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 3-4)
  - Board of Directors: 1979-, 197967 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 5-6)
  - Book of the Month Club, Inc., 197966 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 7)
  - Books and Arts Associates (Asia), 197965 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 8)
  - Books and Arts Associates: Search for Alexander Project, 197964 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 9)
  - Books and Arts Associates, 197963 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 10)
  - Books Direct: Miscellaneous, 197962 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 11)
  - Books Group, 197961 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 12-13)
  - Business 2.0: Edit: 2002-, 197960 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 14)
  - Cable News Network/CNN, 197959 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 15)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1961-1965, 197958 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 16)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1966-1970, 197957 (Offsite-box 454)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1966-1970 [RESTRICTED], 197956 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1971-1989, 197955 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 18-19)
  - Civil Defense & Disaster Survival: 1961-1970, 197954 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 20)
  - Company Services: Aircraft, 197953 (Offsite-box 454)
  - Company Services: Aircraft [RESTRICTED], 197952 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Company Services: Miscellaneous, 197951 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 22)
  - Consumer Marketing: 1990 & Later, 197950 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 23)
  - Cooking Light: Edit & Pub.: 1986-, 197949 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 24)
  - Copy Processing: 1980-, 197948 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Affairs: 1972: Promotion Conference: Nov. 1-3, 1972, 197947 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 26)
  - Corporate Affairs: General, 197946 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Affairs: Staff Meetings: 1969-1974, 197945 (Offsite-box 454, Folder 28)
  - Corporate Affairs: Staff Meetings: 1975-1977, 197944 (Offsite-box 454-455)
  - Corporate Communications: 1989-, 197943 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Controller, 197942 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Development: 1961-1962, 197941 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Development: 1963, 197940 (Offsite-box 455, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Development: 1964, 197939 (Offsite-box 455)
  - Corporate Development: 1964 [RESTRICTED], 197938 (Offsite-box R4)
  - Corporate Development: 1965, 197937 (Offsite-box 455)
  - Corporate Development: 1965 [RESTRICTED], 197936 (Offsite-box R4)